<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="150dp"
            android:orientation="horizontal">

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/imageView2"
                android:layout_width="100dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_weight="1"
                android:padding="5dp"
                app:srcCompat="@drawable/cute_dog_1" />

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:layout_weight="1"
                android:orientation="vertical">

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView2"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_weight="1"
                    android:text="Story Title 1"
                    android:textStyle="bold" />

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView20"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_weight="1"
                    android:text="Date: December 5, 2020" />
            </LinearLayout>

        </LinearLayout>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView24"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:text="Don't talk to me about hours, what about sudo, man? How are we gonna get that? You think the meth fairy is gonna just bring it to us? God it takes me a week to get this stuff. I'm driving all the way up to Las Cruces, two hundred miles each way to meet up with my Smurfs. The dudes who go to the drug stores and get a couple boxes at a time and then sell 'em to me. And that's maybe only good for, like a half pound worth. See that's the bottle neck in your brilliant business plan. Of course you would've known that if you would've just asked me.   Oh c'mon, this is bullshit! I mean look at this dude, alright? He doesn't even know what planet he's living on! You ever, have like a wild animal trapped in your house? Opossum - big, freaky, lookin' bitch. Hey, since when did they change it to opossum? What's up with that? When I was comin' up it was just possum. Opossum makes it sound like he's Irish or something. Why do they gotta go changing everything?   Oh well, heil Hitler, bitch! And let me tell you something else. So what're you saying? Like, I shot someone with, like, a gun? We flipped a coin, okay? You and me. You and me! Coin flip is sacred! Your job is waiting for you in that basement, as per the coin!    I took this vo-tech class in high school, woodworking. I took a lot of vo-tech classes, because it was just big jerk-off, but this one time I had this teacher by the name of... Mr... Mr. Pike. I guess he was like a Marine or something before he got old. He was hard hearing. My project for his class was to make this wooden box. You know, like a small, just like a... like a box, you know, to put stuff in. So I wanted to get the thing done as fast as possible. "
            android:padding="5dp"/>

    </LinearLayout>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>